https://www.hi2cosmetics.com/shop/index.php?l=page_view&p=privacy_policy

Categories
BEAUTY OFFERS on Selected ProductsMAKE-UP PACKSCleansers & LotionsFace CreamsMasksPeelingsEye CareBody CareHand CareLip CareAmpoulesSerums SUN CAREKEENWELL - OXIDANCE LineKEENWELL - OPTIMA LineKEENWELL -EVOLUTION SPHERES LineKEENWELL - AQUASPHERA LineKEENWELL - TENSILFT-STEM CELL LineKEENWELL - WHITENING CARELADY ESTHER - NATURAL LineLADY ESTHER - ARTBIO STEM CELL LineLADY ESTHER - ANTI-AGEING MATRIXYL LineLADY ESTHER - SENSITIVE LineLADY ESTHER - ACNE TREATMENTLADY ESTHER - ACTIVE FORMULA LineLADY ESTHER - CAVIAR LineLADY ESTHER - OXYGENIUM Line LADY ESTHER
- VITAMINSANTI AGING HYALLURONIC ACID PRODUCTSROYAL JELLY Line
Gift Certificates
Privacy Policy
About Us
Contact Us
Cart Contents
0 Item(s) €0.00
Home » Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Effective Date: 22/05/2018
This Policy defines the scope of privacy and degree of confidentiality protecting the information provided by users during registration and normal use of hi2cosmetics.com (“Site”), H-2 Cosmetics Ltd services, programs and facilities. At any time, users can, at their discretion, allow or forbid collection and use of their personal information.
This Policy applies to Site owned and operated by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd, a Cyprus based and Registered corporation, and its affiliates (collectively, “Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd”). By using the Site, user provides his/her consent that Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd has the authority to collect, use and disclose the user’s personal information according to the rules of this Policy.
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd proclaims and accepts its responsibility to protect the user’s personal information. This document contains the rules upon which such information is collected and used, and also the reasons for disclosure of such information. These rules apply to any personal information collected by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd.
1. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
During work with the Site, technical non-personal information about the user such as the user’s IP address, address of another site the user came to the Site from, time of the visit, and browser type and language version, may be collected automatically. We may also collect and analyze navigational information, namely the address and path of the user through the Site, actions performed at the Site, jumps to and from inner links, etc.
Personal information of the User is collected only upon prior permission from the User to collect and use certain information within these rules. Giving such permission, the User supplies such information voluntarily.
"Personal information" includes:
Information supplied by the user during registration at the Site, including the login, full name and e-mail. When user registers on the Site, Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd collects additional information such as postal address and contact phone number;
Information supplied by the User during purchase, such as a billing address and the credit card number;
Registered users also have an option to provide additional personal information such as address and phone number within their profiles. Each user can control what information is displayed at “My Account” page.
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd never requires users to provide genetic data, biometric data, information revealing racial or ethnic origin of users, their political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade-union membership, and data concerning their health or sex life or sexual orientation.
Each user has the right to refuse the submission of personal information at any time. However, in this case, some functions and services offered at the Site may be degraded and/or made unavailable, in part or in its entirety.
2. USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Collection and use of the user’s personal information is performed by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd for the following purposes:
Creation, management and maintenance of an account;
Processing of the User's inquiries and operations at the Site;
Customer service;
Data analysis and statistical research for the purposes of improving offered goods, products or technologies;
Provision and display of the content specially chosen in accordance with preferences and interests of the User;
Maintenance of operation of interactive areas;
Realization of communication and contacts on matters concerning transactions made by the User;
Notification about new goods and services to the Site User;
Marketing communications for promotion and advertising of Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd and third-party products.
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd will ask for user’s consent before using his/her personal information for a purpose other than listed in this Policy.
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd collects personal information about its users only, and does not require users to provide Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd with personal information of any third persons, except for case of purchasing Gift Certificates through the Site for a third person or as described below.
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd has the ability to send communications concerning transactions performed by the user, payment reminders and questions concerning purchase confirmation.
Users are free to select one-click opt-out possibility to unsubscribe from promotional and advertising communications. Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd will not further send promotional and advertising messages once objection is received from a user. This one-click subscription is not available for transactional messages that are generally required. To opt-out of communications connected to transactions, users shall deactivate their accounts.
Our promotional and advertising messages will always be clearly identified as promotional and/or advertising, and will always contain both return e-mail address and physical postal address of Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd. This return e-mail address will be capable of receiving user communications for no less than 30 days from the transmission of the original message.
Personal information collected by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd may be processed and stored in other countries at facilities belonging to Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd and/or legally used by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd. Supplying Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd with the personal information, users permit its transfer outside the country within the bounds of such use, provided that privacy laws other countries where the information Is transferred may not be as protective as those in users’ jurisdiction.
3. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Except in situations clearly stated within these rules, Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd does not disclose, sell, lease, lend, rent or make available personal information of the user to any third parties.
Users’ personal information can be disclosed and shared with partner agencies that render services on behalf of Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd. The services may include money transfer, data storage, reselling licenses, payment processing, etc. These third parties will receive only the information required to provide said specific services; the information will be kept and protected by the same principles and level of protection followed by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd, and it cannot be used for any other purposes.
Information about users may also be passed and disclosed as a business asset in the case of acquisition, sale or absorption of the company. In the event of this unlikely case, Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd will inform users in accordance with the procedure outlined below.
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd reserves the right to disclose and pass personal information of the User if it is required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site.
4. ACCESS TO OWN PERSONAL INFORMATION
Information indicated by the User at the Site can be reviewed and edited in the section «Main Menu — My Account». Alternatively, users may contact Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd at info@hi2cosmetics.com and request a copy of information collected by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd to be extracted and provided in a readable format. Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd will respond to such request without unreasonable delay.
We will retain users’ information for as long as their accounts are active or as needed to provide services to users.
Users shall contact us at info@hi2cosmetics.com in order to cancel his or her account or request that we delete or no longer use their information to provide services. In this case, we will retain and use user’s information only to the extent, necessary to comply with our legal obligations, prevention of fraud, resolution of disputes and performance of our agreements.
5. USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. To manage Flash cookies, please click here .
The User can allow or forbid the use and acceptance of cookies on his/her computer. If cookies are blocked by the User, it may prevent the User from being able to register or perform other interactive functions of the Site, but it will not affect the User’s ability to perform general navigation within the Site.
6. PROTECTION OF THE USER'S PERSONAL INFORMATION
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd actively monitors and enforces the information protection standards during all Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd' activity, namely:
Limitation of the rendered access to information only to those employees who need it for providing services to the User;
Signature of confidentiality treaties by employees;
Signature by partners and external companies invited for fulfillment of particular functions of confidentiality treaties and agreements concerning non-use of such information for any unauthorized purposes;
Encryption of payment data such as credit card number using SSL technology through the use of our third-party payment gateway service providers (PAYPAL);
Storing of the personal information obtained from the User in encrypted form, at protected computers secured from unauthorized access.
Since there is no perfect secure method of protecting information during its storage, processing and transfer into electronic form, Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd does not give the full warranty of its complete safety, despite all efforts made by the company. If information of an account and personal data of the User are protected with a password, safety and nondisclosure of this password are responsibility of the User him/herself.
Users also have a right to lodge a complaint with competent supervisory authorities in countries of their residence or location should users consider that any of their privacy rights may be infringed by Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd.
7. MINOR USERS
Site, Site content and services are neither intended to be used by minors and persons under age of 18, nor designed and intended to willfully and knowingly collect, use, or disclose any personal information from minors and persons under age of 18. Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd will immediately remove personal information from children and/or search to obtain a verifiable parental consent for the collection use, or disclosure of personal information from children, once it will come to Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd’ attention that any personal information from children was submitted or collected through the Site.
The User confirms and warrants that he/she has reached the age of 18, has all the sufficient for usage of the Site and is bound by legal obligations sufficient for any liability that can appear as a result of usage of the Site files. The User agrees to bear full responsibility for all cases of the Site usage without distinction, as well as for use of his/her login and password by third parties including minors and persons under age of 18 living with him/her.
8. LINKS
The Site pages can contain links to sites, services and functions of third parties, subsidiaries and affiliates that may use and conform to different rules and procedures of confidentiality provision from those stated here. Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd is not responsible for the policy of confidentiality of such resources.
9. BLOGS
Our Site may offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at info@hi2cosmetics.com .
Our blog may also be managed by a third-party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third-party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third-party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.
10. SOCIAL MEDIA WIDGETS
Our Site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and Widgets, such as the Share This button, or interactive mini-programs that run on our Site. These Features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page(s) you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.
11. CHANGES TO THESE RULES
We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any file (or material) changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
12. CONTACT US
For any questions, concerns or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@hi2cosmetics.com.com or via postal mail at P.O.Box 21308, 1506 Nicosia Cyprus.
Both users and persons who don’t use Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd services shall be free to contact Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd with any questions, concerns or suggestions regarding our privacy.
Disclaimer: The original, legally binding version of this document is written in English, and may be translated into other languages. If there are any discrepancies between the English version and a translated version, the English version supersedes the translated version.
Categories
BEAUTY OFFERS on Selected ProductsMAKE-UP PACKSCleansers & LotionsFace CreamsMasksPeelingsEye CareBody CareHand CareLip CareAmpoulesSerums SUN CAREKEENWELL - OXIDANCE LineKEENWELL - OPTIMA LineKEENWELL -EVOLUTION SPHERES LineKEENWELL - AQUASPHERA LineKEENWELL - TENSILFT-STEM CELL LineKEENWELL - WHITENING CARELADY ESTHER - NATURAL LineLADY ESTHER - ARTBIO STEM CELL LineLADY ESTHER - ANTI-AGEING MATRIXYL LineLADY ESTHER - SENSITIVE LineLADY ESTHER - ACNE TREATMENTLADY ESTHER - ACTIVE FORMULA LineLADY ESTHER - CAVIAR LineLADY ESTHER - OXYGENIUM Line LADY ESTHER
- VITAMINSANTI AGING HYALLURONIC ACID PRODUCTSROYAL JELLY Line
Manufacturers
- Please Select -
Lady Esther CosmeticsKeenwellTheradermZIMBERLANDTAXOR
Bestsellers
Cream Deodorant 50 ml
Hydrosphere H2O
80 ml
Vitamin A Cream 50 ml
Anti Aging Moisture Base 30 ml €45.00 €24.65
Loading Tweets...
Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd - Quality Skin Care for Face and Body - Lady Esther - Keenwell ©Copyright 2020 Hi-2 Cosmetics Ltd   -   Powered by SunShop "Shopping Cart Software"
